Guide to the Salo W. Baron Papers, 1900-1980
Department of Special Collections
- Series 3. Archival Materials, 13 linear ft. (26 boxes)
  - GPStA; AA I Rep. I; Türkei; no. 65 vol. I, II; transcripts of documents; Christian and Jewish communities in the Middle East (1838-46); part IV1838-46 (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - GPStA; AA I Rep. I; Türkei; no. 65 vol. I, II; transcripts of documents; Christian and Jewish communities in the Middle East (1838-46); part V1838-46 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - GPStA, AA I Rep. I; Türkei; no. 65-85; transcripts of documents, Christian and Jewish communities in the Middle East (1838-46); part VI1838-46 (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - GPStA; AA I Rep. I; Türkei; no. 65 vol. I, II; transcripts of documents; Christian and Jewish communities in the Middle East (1838-46); part VII1838-46 (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - GPStA; AA I Rep. I; Türkei; no. 3-85; transcripts of documents; Christian and Jewish communities in the Middle East (1838-46); part VIII1838-46 (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - GPStA; AA Zentral-Bureau I A, Bq 2, vol. XIII-XXII; transcripts of documents; Christian and Jewish communities in the Middle East (1838-46)1838-46 (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - GPStA; AA I A, Bq 9; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in East Prussia (1822-42)1822-42 (Box 178, Folder 10)
  - GPStA; AA Rep. 89B VIII; Bq VIII 20/1; Rep. 74-89 (misc.); transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in East Prussia (1822-42)1822-42 (Box 178, Folder 11)
  - GPStA; AA Zentral Bureau, I A Bq 9; Rep. 89B VIII; Rep. 77 XXX; AA Sect. III Rep. XVI; handwritten notes, notes in Hebrew (Box 178, Folder 12)
  - GPStA; AA Rep. 76 II; Rep. 77 XXX; Rep. 89 C XLII; Rep. 74 J IX; misc. photostats; part I (Box 178, Folder 13)
  - GPStA; AA Rep. 76 II; Rep. 77 XXX; Rep. 89 C XLII; Rep. 74 J IX; misc. photostats; part II (Box 178, Folder 14)
  - GPStA; AA Rep. 76 II; Rep. 77 XXX; Rep. 89 C XLII; Rep. 74 J IX; misc. photostats; part III (Box 178, Folder 15)
  - GPStA; misc. photostats; part I (Box 178, Folder 16)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16; Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. 5; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in East Prussia (1817-59)1817-59 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - GPStA; AA III Rep. 89C XIVb; Rep. 89B VIII 20 vol. 1; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in East Prussia (1817-59) 1817-59 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - GPStA; AA III Rep. 77 XXX Gen. no. 46; Rep. XVI I vol. 5; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in East Prussia (1817-59)1817-59 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - GPStA; Rep. 89 C XIV B; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in East Prussia (1817-59)1817-59 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - GPStA; Rep. 89C XIV B; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in East Prussia (1817-59)1817-59 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. I; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna/Bundestag zu Frankfurt; Jews in Posen, Warsaw, German cities and states (1815-17); part I1815-17 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. I; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna/Bundestag zu Frankfurt; Jews in Posen, Warsaw, German cities and states (1815-17); part II1815-17 (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. I; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna/Bundestag zu Frankfurt; Jews in Posen, Warsaw, German cities and states (1815-17); part III1815-17 (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. I; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna/Bundestag zu Frankfurt; Jews in Posen, Warsaw, German cities and states (1815-17); part IV1815-17 (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. I; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna/Bundestag zu Frankfurt; Jews in Posen, Warsaw, German cities and states (1815-17); part V1815-17 (Box 179, Folder 10)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. II; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in East Prussia and Poland (1817-23); part I1817-23 (Box 179, Folder 11)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. II; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in East Prussia and Poland (1817-23); part II1817-23 (Box 179, Folder 12)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. II; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in different states of the German Empire and Austria (1819-47); part III1819-47 (Box 179, Folder 13)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. IV; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in different states of the German Empire and Austria (1819-47)1819-47 (Box 179, Folder 14)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. III-V; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in different states of the German Empire and Austria (1819-47)1819-47 (Box 179, Folder 15)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 3, vol. II; no. 1, vol. III; no. 3 vol. I-II; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in different states of the German Empire and Austria (1819-47)1819-47 (Box 179, Folder 16)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 4; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in different states of the German Empire and Austria (1819-47)1819-47 (Box 179, Folder 17)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. VII; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in Eastern Europe (Ottoman Empire, 1848-59) and the U.S. (1855-61)1855-61 (Box 179, Folder 18)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. VIII; no. 3, vol. I; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in Eastern Europe (Ottoman Empire, 1848-59) and the U.S. (1855-61)1855-61 (Box 179, Folder 19)
  - GPStA, AA I, Rep. 5, no. 00; Rep. 75 A J 6; transcripts of documents; civil status of Jews in Frankfurt a.M., Bremen, Lübeck, (1819-21)1819-21 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - GPStA, AA, Rep. 6 I J no. Ia; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna (1814-15); part I1814-15 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - GPStA, AA, Rep. 6 I J no. 1a; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna (1814-15); part II1814-15 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - GPStA, AA, Rep. 6 I J no. 1a; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna (1814-15); part III1814-15 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - GPStA; AA, Rep. 6, V, no. 2; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna; civil status of Jews in German cities, esp. Frankfurt a.M. (1819-20)1819-20 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - GPStA; AA Rep. XVI, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. 1; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna; civil status of Jews in Bremen, Lübeck, Hamburg (1815)1815 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - GPStA; AA, Rep. 75, A J 10; transcripts of documents; Bundestag zu Frankfurt (1825)1825 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - GPStA; Rep. 75, AA II; transcipts ofdocuments; Acta der Königlichen Gesandschaft an den Deutschen Bundestag (1816-24)1816-24 (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - GPStA; Rep. 75 A J 6; transcipts of documents; Acta der Königlichen Gesandschaft an den Deutschen Bundestag (1820); Gewerbliche Ausweisung der Juden aus Bremen und Lübeck; plus miscellanea1820 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - GPStA; transcripts of documents; civil status of Jews in Frankfurt (1815-24); part I1815-24 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - GPStA; transcripts of documents; civil status of Jews in Frankfurt (1815-24); part II1815-24 (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - GPStA; transcripts of documents; civil status of Jews in Frankfurt (1815-24); part III1815-24 (Box 180, Folder 12)
  - GPStA; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in Prussia and Poland (1817-29)1817-29 (Box 180, Folder 13)
  - Acta der Königlichen Gesandschaft an den Deutschen Bundestag in Frkft. a. M. (1820); copies; part I1820 (Box 180, Folder 14)
  - Acta der Königlichen Gesandschaft an den Deutschen Bundestag in Frkft. a. M. (1820); copies; part II1820 (Box 180, Folder 15)
  - Excerpts from: Die Deutsche Bundesakte (Box 180, Folder 16)
  - Stadtarchiv Frankfurt a.M.; photocopies of documents; Jewish community in Frankfurt (17th and 18th centuries); part I (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Stadtarchiv Frankfurt a.M.; photocopies of documents; Jewish community in Frankfurt (17th and 18th centuries); part II (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Stadtarchiv Frankfurt a.M.; photocopies of documents; Jewish community in Frankfurt (17th and 18th centuries); part III (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Stadtarchiv Frankfurt a.M.; photocopies of documents; Jewish community in Frankfurt (17th and 18th centuries); part IV (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Stadtarchiv Frankfurt a.M.; photocopies of documents; Jewish community in Frankfurt (17th and 18th centuries); part V (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Stadtarchiv Frankfurt a.M.; photocopies of documents; Jewish community in Frankfurt (17th and 18th centuries); part VI (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Würtembergisches Staatsarchiv; Deutscher Bund; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna (1816-24)1816-24 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Stadtarchiv Frankfurt; Acta Senatorum, A 168, 169, M 16; transcripts of documents and photostats; Jewish community in Frankfurt (1817-21); part I1817-21 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Stadtarchiv Frankfurt; Acta Senatorum, A 168, 169, M 16; transcripts of documents and photostats; Jewish community in Frankfurt (1817-21); part II1817-21 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Archive?; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in different German city states (1814-21); part I1814-21 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Archive?; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in different German city states (1814-21); part II1814-21 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Archive?; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna; Jewish communities in Hamburg, Bremen, Lübeck (1815-16); part I, 1815-16 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Archive?; transcripts of documents; Congress of Vienna; Jewish communities in Hamburg, Bremen, Lübeck (1815-16); part II1815-16 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - transcripts of miscellaneous documents; Jews in Frankfurt (1843)1843 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Bremisches Staatsarchiv; handwritten notes (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Various archives; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in Lübeck and Bremen (ca.1815-25)ca.1815-25 (Box 182, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts of documents; Jewish community in Lübeck (1815-21)1815-21 (Box 182, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous documents; Lübeck (ca. 1815-20)1815-20 (Box 182, Folder 12)
  - GPStA; Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I, no. 1, vol. I; transcripts of miscellaneous documents; Jewish communities in the Hansastädte (ca. 1815-20)1815-20 (Box 182, Folder 13)
  - Notebook; Jews in Lübeck and Hamburg (Box 182, Folder 14)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I no. 1-5; photostats; part I (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - GPStA; AA III, Rep. 16, Polizei-Sachen Juden I no. 1-5; photostats; part II (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - GPStA; Rep. 89 C XIVb no. 19-; photostats (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - GPStA; AA I, Rep. I, Türkei; photostats; part I (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - GPStA; AA I, Rep. I, Türkei; photostats; part II (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - GPStA; AA I, Rep. I, Türkei; photostats; part III (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Photostats; Jewish communities in German cities (1815-21)1815-21 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Haus-, Hof- und Staatsarchiv Wien (=HHStW); Staatskanzlei Consulate, fasc. 36, 38; transcripts of documents; New York (1830-52)1830-52 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - HHStW; Consulate, fasc. 38; transcripts of documents; Bucarest (1850-64)1850-64 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Vienna Archive; Constantinople, Rapports, VI, fasc. 53-67; fasc. 36; New York Consular Reports; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in the Middle East and Eastern Europe (1840-64); part I1840-64 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Vienna Archive; Constantinople, Rapports, VI, fasc. 53-67; fasc. 36; New York Consular Reports; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in the Middle East and Eastern Europe (1840-64); part II1840-64 (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - HHStW; Türkei, fasc, 57, 58, 59, 61; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in the Middle East (1841-42)1841-42 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Vienna Archive; Constantinople, Rapports VI, fasc. 53-67; Index Staatskanzlei 1830; F.O. documents; handwritten notes1830 (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Vienna Archive; transcripts of documents; Jewish religious schools (1812)1812 (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Vienna Archive; transcripts of documents; Jews in Galatz (1859)1859 (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - Archive?; photocopies of Hebrew Codices (no. 74, 175, 4954, 134) (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - Austrian National Library Vienna; photoreproduction in colour (negative) of Hebrew Codex (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - HHStW; Staatskanzlei, Consulate; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in the Middle East (1840); part I1840 (Box 184, Folder 11)
  - HHStW; Staatskanzlei, Consulate; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in the Middle East (1840); part II1840 (Box 184, Folder 12)
  - HHStW; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in the Middle East and elsewhere (1828-48) (Box 184, Folder 13)
  - HHStW; Staatskanzlei 1836-41 and others; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in the Middle East and the Hapsburg Empire (1836-49)1836-49 (Box 184, Folder 14)
  - Vienna State Archive; photocopies of Hebrew Codices; part I (Box 184, Folder 15)
  - Vienna State Archive; photocopies of Hebrew Codices; part II (Box 184, Folder 16)
  - U.S.-Palestine (ca. 1860-80); handwritten notes1860-80 (Box 184, Folder 17)
  - Haus-, Hof- und Staatskanzlei Wien (=HHStW); Staatskanzlei, Deutsche Akten; transcripts of documents; civil status of Jews in Frankfurt (1818-24)1818-24 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - HHStW; Rapporte, Türkei; Staatskanzlei, Consulate; miscellaneous type- and handwritten notes (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - HHStW; Staatskanzlei 1820-46; transcripts of documents; Jewish communities in the Hapsburg Empire1820-46 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - HHStW; Staatskanzlei 1820-43; miscellaneous transcripts; Jewish communities in the Hapsburg Empirepart I1820-46 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - HHStW; Staatskanzlei 1820-43; miscellaneous transcripts; Jewish communities in the Hapsburg, Ottoman, and Russian Empires; part II1820-46 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Vienna Archive; transcripts of documents; civil status of Jews in Romania (1930)1930 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous excerpts from Aus Metternichs nachgelassenen Papieren, 1816-481816-48 (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - HHStW; Staatskanzlei 1841-43; transcripts of documents; Italian Jews1841-43 (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Netherlands; Buitlandsche Zaken Catalog (=BZC); Suppl. I no. 1750, Dossier A no. 26; photostats and transcripts of documents (1815-43); part I1815-43 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Buitlandsche Zaken Catalog (=BZC); Suppl. I no. 1750, Dossier A no. 26; photostats and transcripts of documents (1815-43); part II1815-43 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Buitlandsche Zaken Catalog (=BZC); Suppl. I no. 1750, Dossier A no. 26; photostats and transcripts of documents (1815-43); part III1815-43 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Buitlandsche Zaken Catalog (=BZC); Suppl. I no. 1750, Dossier A no. 26; photostats and transcripts of documents (1815-43); part IV1815-43 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Buitlandsche Zaken Catalog (=BZC); Suppl. I no. 1750, Dossier A no. 26; photostats and transcripts of documents (1815-43); part V1815-43 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Buitlandsche Zaken Catalog (=BZC); Suppl. I no. 1750, Dossier A no. 26; photostats and transcripts of documents (1815-43); part VI1815-43 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Buitlandsche Zaken Catalog (=BZC); Suppl. I no. 1750, Dossier A no. 26; photostats and transcripts of documents (1815-43); part VII1815-43 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Universiteits-Bibliothek Amsterdam; photoreproduction of documents (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - Israel; Jewish National and University Library (Jerusalem); photoreproductions of documents (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Jerusalem Archive?; photocopies of documents; Financial support of Jews in Palestine by American and English Jewish communities (1849-79); part I1849-79 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Jerusalem Archive?; photocopies of documents; Financial support of Jews in Palestine by American and English Jewish communities (1849-79); part II1849-79 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - The Jewish Historical General Archive (JHGA), Jerusalem; photocopies of documents; the Jewish community in Rome (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - JHGA; photocopies of documents; Antwerpen (1608-1610)1608-1610 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - JHGA; photocopies of documents; formerly: codice Vaticano and other Italian collections (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts and photostats of documents in Hebrew and English; Jerusalem (5599-5609 = 1839-49 A.D.); part I1839-49 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - transcripts and photostats of documents in Hebrew and English; Jerusalem (5599-5609 = 1839-49 A.D.); part II1839-49 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - transcripts and photostats of documents in Hebrew and English; Jerusalem (5599-5609 = 1839-49 A.D.); part III1839-49 (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - transcripts and photostats of documents in Hebrew and English; Jerusalem (5599-5609 = 1839-49 A.D.); part IV1839-49 (Box 187, Folder 10)
  - Catalog: Hebräische Inkunabeln 1475-14941475-1494 (Box 187, Folder 11)
  - miscellaneous transcripts and photostats (Box 187, Folder 12)
  - Excerpts from: Aus dem Geschäftsbericht der General Mortgage Bank of Palestine, LTD für 19401940 (Box 187, Folder 13)
  - The Hebrew University of Jerusalem; photocopies of documents; Jewish communities in Spain (14th and 15th centuries)14th and 15th centuries (Box 187, Folder 14)
  - National Library Jerusalem; Heb 8 0 259; photostats of a Hebrew codex (Box 187, Folder 15)
  - Original document: "Priere des Membres du Santjedrin(?) recitée dans leurs assemblée convoquée à Paris (9. Feb. 1807)9. Feb. 1807 (Box 187, Folder 16)
  - Transcripts of Hebrew documents (Box 187, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper articles, pamphlets, reports, original documents and transcripts of documents; Jews in Romania (1911-20)1911-20 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clips from: La Roumanie (21 March 1928); Journal des Débats (7 July 1919); Le Pays (6 July 1919)1919, 1928 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - "Chronology of Anti-Semitism in Roumania, 1926-27"; Extrait du journal Vütorul de Bucarest (26 Dec. 1919); miscellanea1926-27 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts of newspaper articles on Jews in Romania (1938); original flyer of Romanian fascists (undated)1938 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts of protocols of Jewish organizations in Romania (ca. 1920); statements of members of the Austrian (?) parliament regarding Romanian Jews (undated)1920 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - "Petition des Juifs indigenes au Parlement" (undated); various statements and documentations on the Jewish question in Romania (original documents); photos of newspaper articles (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Pamphlets in Hebrew; Jews in Romania (1930's)1930's (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Das kooperative Vort, issues no. 1,2,3,4,5,7 (1930); photo of Romanian fascists; pamphlet "Biblioteca de Vulgarisare", no. 6 (1927)1927, 1930 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Bukowinaer Volkszeitung (24 Jan. 1930)24 Jan. 1930 (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - Report on Jews in Romania (undated)undated (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - "Stenographisches Protokoll der ... Jüdischen Wirtschaftskonferenz für die Bukowina" (15 June 1930)15 June 1930 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings amd pamphlets regarding Romanian Jews (19th. c.)19th. c. (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Letters regarding Romanian Jews (19th c.); original documents; photo of Jacob Psantir (1887)1887 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Reports in German and Hebrew regarding Romanian Jews (19th c.)19th c. (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings, pamphlets and reports on Romanian Jews (19th c.); original documents19th c. (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Reports on Jews in Kischinew (1903); original documents; part I1903 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Reports on Jews in Kischinew (1903); original documents; part II1903 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Reports on Jews in Kischinew (1903); original documents; part III1903 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Correspondance Paris - New York on Jewish emigrants from Europe (1907-)1907- (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - Pamphlet on anti-semitic pogroms in Moldavia (1907); flyer of the Romania "Liga Antisemitica" (1907); original documents1907 (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - Pamphlets in Romanian on the Jewish Question; report in German on anti-semitic pogroms in Romania (ca. 1900-1910); original documents1900-1910 (Box 189, Folder 11)
  - Pamphlets and reports on the Jews in Romania (ca. 1915); original documents1915 (Box 189, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous material (reports, printed matter, letters) on Romanian Jews (1930-)1930 (Box 189, Folder 13)
  - Pamphlet of the "Collegio Israelita de Mexico" (1946)1946 (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - "Catalogo degli Ebrei Russi" (ca. 1835); transcripts of Russian documents1835 (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts of Russian documents (19th c.)19th c. (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Moscow Archive; handwritten notes (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Eight notebooks: "Corfu-Material" (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous transcripts from German and English archives (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous notes from German and Dutch archives (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous transcripts from German and Dutch archives (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - Documentation "Juden und Antisemitismus in Deutschland" (1959)1959 (Box 190, Folder 10)
  - Photos of the documentation "Juden ..." (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - Photos of Birobigan (U.S.S.R.?) (Box 190, Folder 12)
  - Protocol of the "Secret Session of Young Elders of Zion" by Charles Recht (Box 190, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous transcripts (Box 190, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper clippings from Fun (1872); The New York Times (19 March 1943)1872, 1943 (Box 190, Folder 15)
  - Transcript of "Norme sulle communità israelitiche e sulla unione delle comunità medesime" (30 Oct. 1930)1930 (Box 190, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous material; German Archives, 19th c.; 119th c. (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous material; German Archives, 19th c.; 219th c. (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous material; German Archives, 19th c.; 319th c. (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous material; German Archives, 19th c.; 419th c. (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous material; German Archives, 19th c.; handwritten notes19th c. (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - F. O. documents, misc. transcripts (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Agreement: Policies; Amsterdam, 17th of Nov. 1790; reproduction of document and transcript1790 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - Frankfurt City Archive; "Aufnahme der Juden in die Stättigkeit 1496-1514"; 1-41496-1514 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Frankfurt City Archive; "Aufnahme der Juden in die Stättigkeit 1496-1514"; 5-81496-1514 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Frankfurt City Archive; "Aufnahme der Juden in die Stättigkeit 1496-1514"; 9-121496-1514 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Frankfurt City Archive; "Aufnahme der Juden in die Stättigkeit 1496-1514"; 13-161496-1514 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Venetian State Archive; part I (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Venetian State Archive; part II (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Venetian State Archive; part III (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Venetian State Archive; part IV (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Venetian State Archive; part V (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Venetian State Archive; part V (duplicate) (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Madrid Archives; Inquisition documents (Box 192, Folder 11)
  - Madrid Library; unlabeled microfilms (Box 192, Folder 12)
  - Madrid National Library; MS 5767; 13043; 2421; 4013 (Box 192, Folder 13)
  - Lisbon National Library; Inquisition documents? (Box 192, Folder 14)
  - Lisbon Archives (Arquivo Nacional da Torre do Tombo); Inquisition documents (Box 192, Folder 15)
  - Amsterdam; Polemical tract against Christianity in Hebrew (Box 192, Folder 16)
  - Amsterdam; Responsa of Amsterdam; Leghorn, Venice rabbis (1680-1700) with Spanish translation certified by Johannes Leusden; mentions Jacob Sasportas, Moses Zacuto et al.; marital suit against an unnamed Marrano (Box 192, Folder 17)